[Music]
based on the results of the OJK survey, it
appears that the level of financial literacy in
society is still lower
than the level of inclusion.
Therefore, understanding related to
financial literacy is very much
needed and must be immediately
implemented in all levels of
society. Insurance and Prestasi
Junior Indonesia again present the
Spark The Dream program by
providing various series of
financial literacy education activities in 11 schools
in seven cities in this second year. IWD
Insurance wants this program to be expanded
to cities outside Jakarta
so that the financial literacy education that we
do can reach more and more
high school children. This is
extraordinary with the synergy of the elements of the
educational ecosystem from the
driving elements outside the world of education can
contribute related to how
financial literacy can be instilled
in
children. Nowadays, the
culture of f is really booming or if
for example there is a trend, it will
immediately be followed so that consumer behavior falls
even without their parents knowing, it has
become very easy to
do e-transactions, buying and selling
and so on. There I started
to learn like Oh, it turns out that
financial literacy is important for
people's lives, like buying and selling and
so on,
they are guided by volunteers from
FBD, including  also then pour
various kinds of
understanding into a work
that is intended to
share education to educate
teenagers to manage their finances
which are also connected with parents
who can do various things
such as tasks and CH to get
extra pocket money e disappear first
for the social challenge 2024 final
to plusar
Jaya we are very proud we can be
here now first place But we can't be
too satisfied E and of course will
continue to develop our products
seeing the team that is definitely the younger siblings, yes, they are still very
small but already have
extraordinary ideas and creativity ee so we
can see Indonesia in the future
hopefully Eh this event will
continue E and more e scaling up again
if possible to all of Indonesia we are the
FW generation